It feels really good.
すごく良い感じです
Hey, it felt good.
ねえ、気持ちよかったのに
Eh...what do you mean?
え...どういうこと?
What do you mean?
どういうこと?
Don't say uh...
え...と言わないで
You didn't say that.
言ってないでしょ
Said said.
言った言った
One more time.
もう一回
I think I'll start doing it now.
今からやろうかなって
I told you.
言ったよね
said.
言 った
Said.
言った
That's what I said.
言 った って
I told you.
言ったって
I mean, look at me now.
だって俺、今から見てよ
Because I did it.
やったんだからさ
I don't like it.
嫌だ
No, it's not that I don't like it, but I'll try it again.
いや、嫌だじゃなくてもう一回やんの
Well, I started the fire.
え、だって火をつけたの
Which do you think it is?
どっちだって思ってるの?
But it's moving.
でも動いてるよね
It's moving, isn't it?
動いてるよね
There's no need to do it now.
今更は無しだな
I guess so.
ねえかな
It's different.
違うの
It's not really moving.
まじで動いてないな
I added this.
これ、加えてたんだよ
this.
これ
Look at the taste of the table.
台の味、ほら
Look, this was included.
ほら、これ入ってたんだよ
Look.
ほ ら
Yeah.
うん
I remembered.
思い出した
I was adding it to my side.
横んで加えてたよ
横んで加えてたんだよ
It's not moving.
動 いてない
Hey.
ねえ
Let's do more.
もっとやろうぜ
Hey.
ねえ
See, this is how I did it.
ほら、こうやってやってたんださ
I got drunk.
酔っぱらったよ
I did it on purpose.
こっちがあえてしてやったんだぜ
I have to give my impressions.
感想しなきゃ
Look.
ほら
It feels good, right?
気持ちいいだろ
Here, open it.
ほら、開けよ
Show me.
見せろよ
Here, point it.
ほら、向けろよ
You're asking me if I like it.
好きかって聞いてるんだろ
How many people have you worked with so far?
今まで何人とやったことあるの?
Head this way.
こっち向けよ
I'm asking how many people you've worked with.
何人とやったことあるのって聞いてるんだよ
Well then, there you go.
じゃあ、ほら
I'm going to become a celebrity, somebody.
芸能人になるんだよ、誰か
She's an idol, right?
アイドルやってるんだろ
Isn't there a connection?
つながりとかあんじゃねえの?
Hey.
ねえ
It's great to be an idol.
アイドルってやると最高だぜ
Don't hide it.
隠すなよ
Sit down, here.
座れよ、ほら
That's a nice photo.
いい写真だろ
It would be terrible if it was broken.
バラされたらやばいよな
Hey.
なあ
A photo like this.
こんな写真
Yeah.
うん
If it doesn't come when it's released, add it.
バラされたら来なかったら加えろよ、
Look.
ほら
This is not a good photo.
いい写真じゃない、これ
I guess you've added something.
加えたことあるんだろ
Look here, here.
こっち見ろ、ほら
Look.
ほら
Shall I tell you?
教えてやろうか
This is it.
こうだよ
Here, do it.
ほら、やれ
I'll break it down, dude.
バラすぞ、おい
Yes, yes, see.
そうだ、そうだ、ほら
Add it deeper, here.
もっと奥まで加えろ、ほら
Look, look here.
ほら、こっち見ろよ、ほら
Hey, look.
ほら、見ろって
Look at this.
見て、これ
You look really nice.
めっちゃいい顔してんじゃん
Ah.
な あ
It's deeper, see.
もっと奥だよ、ほら
Here, put your hands down.
ほら、手を下つけ
Put your hands down, here.
手を下ろせ、ほら
That's how you eat, you know.
そうやって食えるんだよ、ほら
It's deeper, see.
もっと奥だよ、ほら
Look, it's deeper, look.
ほら、もっと奥だよ、ほら
Look.
ほら
More, see.
もっとだよ、ほら
Look.
ほら
You see?
わかったか、ほら
Look.
ほら
If you don't do it, I'll push you deep inside.
やらないと奥まで突っ込むぞ
You can put it in.
入れてもいいよな
Hey.
なあ
Okay, look.
いいよな、ほら
Wake up.
起きろって
Stand up.
立てよ
See you again.
また、ほら
Look, look.
ほら、ほら
It's backwards, you see.
逆向きだよ、ほら
You seemed to be listening to what I was saying.
言うこと聞くようにあったじゃねえか
I guess you want to tell me if it feels good here too.
ここも気持ちいいのかって 言いたいんだろ、
Hey.
おい
Does it feel good here?
ここが気持ちいいのか?
Does it feel good here too?
ここも気持ちいいのか?
Good boy, don't be quiet
いい子、静かにするんじゃねえ
mosquito.
か
I guess you're sleeping well now.
これで いいさと寝てんだろ
Hey.
なあ
It's facing the opposite way.
反対向きだよ
Spread your legs.
脚広げろよ
Spread it out.
広げろ
Hey, did you spread it out?
ほら、広げたか?
Look.
ほら
Did you spread it?
広げたか?
Here, spread it out.
ほら、広げろ
Look, ass.
ほら、見ろ、ケツ
I'll spread it out, come on.
俺が広げてやるよ、ほら
I guess he just moved it on his own.
おのずみどり動かしてやったんじゃねえか
Spread your legs.
脚広げろよ
Did you spread it?
広げたか?
Hey, go to sleep, come on.
おれ、寝ろよ、ほら
Spread your legs, come on.
脚広げろ、ほら
It's your business power, you know.
お前の商売力だよ、ほら
It's Mike, look.
マイクだよ、ほら
Stop it!
やめろよ
Get used to this.
これ、慣れろ
I'll just delete the photo.
ただ写真消してやるよ
Do well, here.
うまくやれよ、ほら
Spread it out, here.
広げろ、ほら
Hey, I won't erase it unless you do it properly.
おい、ちゃんとやらないと消さないぞ
Spread your legs, come on.
脚広げろ、ほら
Spread it out.
広げろ
Ah, nice.
あー、いいね
Ah, that's a nice photo.
あー、いい写真だ
Come on, make it stronger.
ほら、もっと強くしろ
Hey, don't go on your own.
おれ、勝手に行くなよ
Who will delete the photo?
誰が写真消すか?
Which one feels better? Look.
どっちが気持ちいいかな、ほら
Hey, let me do it manually.
おれ、手動かせよ
Look, don't close it, look.
ほら、閉じんなよ、ほら
It really makes me hungry.
マジで腹持てるよ
I,
お れ、
Does it feel good?
気 持ちいいかな?
It feels good.
気持ちいいよ
Please let me out, right?
出してください、だろ、ほら
No, look.
いや、ほら
Please take it out.
出してください